(Amy:)So what happened?
How'd it go?
(Bernadette:)It's fine. I thanked them again and
let them know we're not available.
(Amy:)So I can drink this without having
to give up the goodies?
Yes, ifs all cool.
Although, it you wanted to talk to
one of them, no one would blame you.
(Amy:)And why would no one blame me?
(Bernadette:)I don't know what I'm saying.
(Amy:)Well, it sounds like you're saying
that I could do better than Sheldon.
Boy, these drinks are strong!
Oh, Mama, I'm gonna be
hugging the toilet tonight!
(Amy:)No, tell me. I want to know
what you meant by that.
(Bernadette:)I just meant that you're not married,
and your boyfriends
kind of... Sheldon.
(Amy:)And your husband is extremely Howard.
What's your point?
(Bernadette:)Sorry, I have no point.
That was a stupid thing to say.